horoscope-daily-free.net 2018-06-05

# 

Horoscope-Daily-Free.net Privacy Policy Last update February, 2015. Horoscope-Daily-Free.net ("we" or Horoscope-Daily-Free.net") has created this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. This privacy policy describes how Horoscope-Daily-Free.net collects and uses the Personal Data you provide on our website. We realize the importance of feeling safe online and want you to feel comfortable using our personalized products and services (collectively, "Offerings") and exchanging information on websites of Horoscope-Daily-Free.net its affiliates or agents ("Company" or "We") with links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "Website"). 1\. QUESTIONS; CONTACTING COMPANY; REPORTING VIOLATIONS If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about our Privacy Policy or our data collection or processing practices, or if you want to report any security violations to us, please contact us at the following mail address: Email: nikk976@gmail.com 2\. USER CONSENT By submitting Personal Data through our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 3\. A NOTE TO USERS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES If you are a non-U.S. user of the Website by visiting the Website or providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your Personal Data may be processed for the purposes identified in the Privacy Policy. In addition, your Personal Data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By providing your data, you consent to such transfer. If you’re a user or visitor in the European Economic Area these rights also apply to you: For the purposes of applicable EU data protection law (including the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the “GDPR”), we are a ‘data controller’ of your personal information. How you can access your personal information You are also entitled to ask us to port your personal information (i.e. to transfer in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, to you), to erase it, or restrict its processing. You also have rights to object to some processing that is based on our legitimate interests, such as profiling that we perform for the purposes of direct marketing, and, where we have asked for your consent to process your data, to withdraw this consent as more fully described below. These rights are limited in some situations – for example, we can demonstrate that we have a legal requirement to process your personal information. In some instances, this means that we may retain some data even if you withdraw your consent. Where we require your personal information to comply with legal or contractual obligations, then provision of such data is mandatory: if such data is not provided, then we will not be able to manage our contractual relationship with you, or to meet obligations placed on us. In all other cases, provision of requested personal information is optional. If you have unresolved concerns you also have the right to complain to data protection authorities. The relevant data protection authority will be the data protection authority of the country: (i) of your habitual residence; (ii) of your place of work; or (iii) in which you consider the alleged infringement has occurred. 4\. TYPES OF DATA WE COLLECT We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data from you as described below when you visit our Website, when you send us information or communication. "Personal Data" means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. "Anonymous Data" means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data; Anonymous Data does not permit the identification of individual persons. We may also collect or develop aggregated information, which may include Anonymous Data and Personal Data, provided that such information does not personally identify you or any of our other users ("Aggregated Data"). B. Personal Data Collected via Technology. To make our Company Properties more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect Personal Data from you, including browser type, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. Like most Internet services, we automatically gather this Personal Data and store it in log files each time you visit our Website. C. Application(s). If you use our Offerings on your mobile device, including through our Application(s), we may collect your phone number and the unique device id number. Our mobile homepage lets you store preferences like safe search settings. We may associate these choices with your ID or the mobile device, and you can edit these preferences at any time on our mobile homepage. E. Personal Data That We Collect from You About Others. If you decide to submit information about a third party, we will collect the third party's Personal Data in order to personalize the services for such third party such as our "Tell a Friend" feature. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. Horoscope-Daily-Free.net stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. You or the third party may contact us to request the removal of this information from our database by contacting us at nikk976@gmail.com. F. Advertising. If there is advertising on the Company Properties, such advertising may employ the use of Cookies or other methods to track hits and clickthroughs. We are not responsible for advertiser Cookies or how the information gathered through their use might be used. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp G. Children. We do not intentionally gather Personal Data from users who are under the age of 13. If a child under 13 submits Personal Data to Company and we learn that the Personal Data is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. If you believe that we might have any Personal Data from a child under 13, please contact us at nikk976@gmail.com . H. Information You Provide to Facebook and Other Social Networking Sites. The Company Properties may allow users to access Facebook to interact with friends and to share on Facebook through Wall and friends' News Feeds. If you are already logged into the Company Properties and Facebook or another SNS, when you click on "Connect with Facebook," or a similar connection on another SNS, you will be prompted to merge your profiles. If you are already logged into the Company Properties but not logged into Facebook or another SNS that we support, when you click on "Connect with Facebook," or a similar connection on another SNS, you will be prompted to enter your SNS credentials or to "Sign Up" for the SNS. By proceeding, you are allowing the Company Properties to access your information and you are agreeing to the Facebook or other SNS's Terms of Use in your use of the Company Properties. Conversely, if you are not currently registered as a user of the Company Properties, and you click on "Sign in" using Facebook or another SNS that we support, you will first be asked to enter your Facebook or SNS credentials and then be given the option to register for the Company Properties. In this case, we may receive information from Facebook or another SNS to make it easier for you to create an account ("Account") on the Company Properties and show our relevant content from your Facebook or SNS friends. Once you register on the Company Properties and connect with Facebook or another SNS you will be able to automatically post recent activity back to Facebook or the other SNS. Any information that we collect from your Facebook or other SNS account may depend on the privacy settings you have with that SNS, so please consult the SNS's privacy and data practices. You have the option to disable Facebook Connect at any time by logging into your Account through the Company Properties and going to settings, "About Me," "Linked Accounts," and then unselecting "Facebook." Further, you can edit privacy settings for the reviews that appear on Facebook, or disconnect your Company Properties activity stream by visiting the Facebook Applications Settings page. I. Information Collected Via Technology. • Information Collected by Our Servers. To make our Company Properties more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. • Log Files. As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider ("ISP"), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the Website, track users' movements around the Website, gather demographic information about our user base as a whole, and better tailor our Offerings to our users' needs. For example, some of the information may be collected so that when you visit the Website or the Offerings again, it will recognize you and the information could then be used to serve advertisements and other information appropriate to your interests. Except as noted in this Privacy Policy, we do not link this automatically-collected data to Personal Data. • Cookies. Like many online services, we use Cookies to collect information. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Website. This type of information is collected to make the Website more useful to you and to tailor the experience with us to meet your special interests and needs. • Pixel Tags. In addition, we use "Pixel Tags" (also referred to as clear Gifs, Web beacons, or Web bugs). Pixel Tags are tiny graphic images with a unique identifier, similar in function to Cookies that are used to track online movements of Web users. In contrast to Cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, Pixel Tags are embedded invisibly in Web pages. Pixel Tags also allow us to send e-mail messages in a format users can read, and they tell us whether e-mails have been opened to ensure that we are sending only messages that are of interest to our users. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to a user. We do not tie the information gathered by Pixel Tags to our users' Personal Data. • Collection of Data by Advertisers. We may also use third parties to serve ads on the Company Properties. Certain third parties may automatically collect information about your visits to the Company Properties and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit our Company Properties (but not your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number). They do this by using Cookies, Pixel Tags or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Website and the other sites tracked by these third parties. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, Cookies or Pixel Tags in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of Cookies and other technologies. We do not currently respond to "Do Not Track" signals from web browsers. • Flash LSOs. When we post videos, third parties may use local shared objects, known as "Flash Cookies," to store your preferences for volume control or to personalize certain video features. Flash Cookies are different from browser Cookies because of the amount and type of data and how the data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash Cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash Cookies, click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html. • Mobile Services. We may also collect non-personal information from your mobile device if you have downloaded our Application(s). This information is generally used to help us deliver the most relevant information to you. Examples of information that may be collected and used include your geographic location, how you use the Application(s), and information about the type of device you use. In addition, in the event our Application(s) crashes on your mobile device, we will receive information about your mobile device model software version and device carrier, which allows us to identify and fix bugs and otherwise improve the performance of our Application(s). This information is sent to us as aggregated information and is not traceable to any individual and cannot be used to identify an individual. • Google Analytics. We use Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the Website. Google Analytics uses Cookies to collect information such as how often users visit the Website, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our Website and services. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Website, rather than your name or other personally identifying information. We do not combine the information generated through the use of Google Analytics with your Personal Data. Although Google Analytics plants a persistent Cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit the Website, the Cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Website is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. 5\. USE OF YOUR DATA A. General. In general, Personal Data you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. We use your Personal Data to personalize our Offerings; to deliver personalized information to you; to send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories; to provide you with electronic newsletters; and to send you special offers related to our Offerings and for other marketing purposes of Company or our third party partners, should you opt-in to receive such communications by indicating such preference in your Profile. Your e-mail address together with a password is used to secure your Profile and to make our personalized e-mail services available to you. B. Creation and Use of Anonymous and Aggregated Data. We may create Anonymous Data and Aggregated Data from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We use this Anonymous Data and Aggregated Data for trend analysis, and to better understand patterns of usage so that we may enhance the content of our Offerings and improve Website navigation. We reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Data and Aggregated Data to third party companies in our discretion. For example, demographic and profile data is shared with our advertisers only in the form of Aggregated Data. Aggregated Data helps our advertisers to tailor their services to the collective characteristics of users of the Company Properties. C. IP Addresses. We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Website, and to track trends and statistics. D. Feedback. If you provide feedback on any of our Company Properties to us, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Data. We will collect any information contained in such communication and will treat the Personal Data in such communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 6\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA A. We will share your Personal Data with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell your Personal Data to third parties. B. Corporate Restructuring. We may share some or all of your Personal Data in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution, transition, or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets. In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, Personal Data may also be transferred as a business asset. If another company acquires our Company, business or assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data described in this Privacy Policy. D. Third Party Services. We reserve the right to offer services and products from third party vendors ("Third Party Vendors") to you on the Company Properties, such as via newsletters or special offers, based on the preferences that you identify during the registration process and based on your subsequent preferences. We may share Aggregated Data about our user base with these Third Party Vendors; this information does not identify individual users. We do not link Aggregated Data with Personal Data. E. Third Party Contractors. We may share your Personal Data with third party contractors or service providers ("Third Party Contractors") to provide you with the services that we offer you though the Company Properties; to conduct quality assurance testing; to provide technical support; or to provide specific services in accordance with your instructions. These Third Party Contractors are required not to use your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by us. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Data with our Third Party Contractors for the sole purpose of providing the Company Properties to you. F. Social Networking Sites. Some of our Applications and Offerings may enable you to post content to SNSs (e.g., Facebook or Twitter). If you choose to do this, we will provide information to such SNSs in accordance with your elections. You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for your use of those websites and that it is your responsibility to review the terms of use and privacy policy of the third party provider of such SNSs. We will not be responsible or liable for: (i) the availability or accuracy of such SNSs; (ii) the content, products or services on or availability of such SNSs; or (iii) your use of any such SNSs. G. Other Disclosures. Due to the existing legal regulatory and security environment, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other Personal Data will not be disclosed to third parties under certain circumstances. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under court order, subpoena, or other circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, in the unlikely event we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can (and you authorize us to do so) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. In addition, where we ask for your Personal Data and you are notified that the information we are collecting on that page will be shared with third parties, and in cases where you opt-in to share your Personal Data with third parties, those disclosures and opt-ins will override anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy. Except as set forth above, we will not disclose any of your Personal Data to third parties unless you give us your prior express consent. 7\. SECURITY We have implemented and follow reasonable industry standard technical and procedural measures to protect against unauthorized access and use of your personal information. However, you should know that neither we nor any other website can fully eliminate these risks. 8\. OTHER WEBSITE LINKS The Company Properties contain links to other websites. Our provision of a link to any other website or location, such as Partner Company websites, is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. When you click on such a link, you will leave the Company Properties and go to another website. During this process, another entity may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you. Company has no control over, does not review, and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on links to such outside websites. 9\. SOCIAL MEDIA FEATURES AND WIDGETS Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 10\. UPDATING/DELETING YOUR PROFILE A. Changes to Personal Data. You can view the Personal Data you previously provided by viewing your Profile from your personalized Home Page. You can delete your Profile at any time by clicking on the "delete profile" link. If your personal data changes, you may correct or update, by emailing us at nikk976@gmail.com. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. You may request deletion of your Personal Data by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete any information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. B. Opt-out. If you have chosen to receive personalized messages, newsletters, or promotional communications by e-mail, you can at any time cancel this, or "opt-out," by following the instructions on your personalized Home Page or by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive. Should you decide to opt-out of receiving future mailings, we may share your e-mail address with our Third Party Contractors to ensure that you do not receive further communications from us. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you service-related communications, including notices of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy. C. Cookies. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to accept Cookies from the Company Properties for any of the purposes described above, then you can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting a Cookie from the websites you visit. Consult your browser's technical information. If you do not accept Cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Company Properties or all functionality of the Company Properties. If you have any questions about how to disable or modify Cookies, please let us know at the contact information provided below. D. De-Linking SNSs. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to have your SNS account (e.g., Facebook or Twitter) linked to your Account, then you may de-link the SNS account in the "preferences" section in your Account settings. You may also manage the sharing of certain Personal Data with us when you connect with us through an SNS, such as through Facebook Connect. Please refer to the privacy settings of the SNS to determine how you may adjust our permissions and manage the interactivity between the Company Properties and your social media account or mobile device. E. Applications. You can stop all collection of information by the Application(s) by uninstalling the Application(s). You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. 11\. SERVICE-RELATED ANNOUNCEMENTS Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you service-related announcements (such as, but not limited to, notice that we have changed the Offerings, the Terms of Service, or the Privacy Policy) when we believe it is necessary to do so. You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature, but if you do not wish to receive these announcements, you have the option to delete your Profile. We will not have any liability whatsoever to you for any deletion of your Profile. 12\. DISPUTE RESOLUTION If you believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at [nikk976@gmail.com]. We will do our best to address your concerns. If you feel that your complaint has been addressed incompletely, we invite you to let us know for further investigation. 13\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Website, and we will change the "Last Updated" date above. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. You should consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.
